// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one is NOT a legal variable name?",
    answer: "my-var",
    options: [
      "my-var",
      'my_var',
      "_myvar",
      "Myvar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the correct file extension for Python files?",
    answer: ".py",
    options: [
      ".pyt",
      ".py",
      ".pyth",
      ".pt"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?",
    answer: "print(type(x))",
    options: [
      "print(typeOf(x))",
      "print(typeof(x))",
      "print(typeof x)",
      "print(type(x))"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the correct way to create a function in Python?",
    answer: "def myFunction():",
    options: [
      "create myFunction():",
      "def myFunction():",
      "function myfunction():",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which method can be used to remove any whitespace from both the beginning and the end of a string?",
    answer: "strip()",
    options: [
      "trim()",
      "len()",
      "ptrim()",
      "strip()"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which collection is ordered, changeable, and allows duplicate members?",
    answer: "LIST",
    options: [
      "TUPLE",
      "DICTIONARY",
      "LIST",
      "SET"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which collection does not allow duplicate members?",
    answer: "SET",
    options: [
      "LIST",
      "SET",
      "TUPLE",
      "DICTIONARY"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How do you start writing a for loop in Python?",
    answer: "for x in y:",
    options: [
      "for x in y:",
      "for each x in y:",
      "for x > y:",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which method can be used to replace parts of a string?",
    answer: "replace()",
    options: [
      "replaceString()",
      "replace()",
      "repl()",
      "switch()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
    answer: "upper()",
    options: [
      "upperCase()",
      "upper()",
      "uppercase()",
      "toUpperCase()"
    ]
  },
];